[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "a__reciation",
    "options": ["P", "F", "X"],
    "answer": "P"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "misunderst__d",
    "options": ["Y", "A", "O"],
    "answer": "O"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "_ransforma_ion",
    "options": ["T", "C", "P"],
    "answer": "T"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "exa__eration",
    "options": ["C", "G", "S"],
    "answer": "G"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "respons_b_l_ty",
    "options": ["I", "U", "A"],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "_ommuni_ation",
    "options": ["C", "K", "D"],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "revolutionar_",
    "options": ["W", "S", "Y"],
    "answer": "Y"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "_ompli_ations",
    "options": ["Q", "R", "C"],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "unbel_evab_l_ty",
    "options": ["O", "W", "I"],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "e_traordinary",
    "options": ["S", "X", "F"],
    "answer": "X"
  }
]